



+33 6 01 11 08 21



sabri.abdennader@gmail.com



Déville-lès-Rouen 76250 France



https://www.linkedin.com/in/s abri-abdennader-965110bb/



MY SKILLS

PERSONAL SKILLS

Web Languages

- Typescript/HTML/CSS

Web Frameworks

- Front: React/VueJS
- Back: Express/Symfony

Software Languages

- Java/C#/C/Python/SQL

Versioning Tools

- Bitbucket/Gitlab/Github

Tools

- UX/UI: Figma, Storybook, Photoshop
- Tests: Jest (Unit), Cypress (e2e)
- Postman (API)
- Redux (State Management)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

French English



SABRI ABDENNADER

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER



PROFILE INFO

I have more than four years of experience in developing frontend features in web apps and websites for various clients. I graduated from Sorbonne University in Paris with a bachelor degree in computer science, and also have two master's degrees in financial management and accounting.



WORK EXPERIENCE

MyUnisoft

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

• Development of various features, bug fixes and tests (unit and e2e) for the company's software

Wandi 2020 - 2022

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

 Development of various functionalities for clients' web applications: responsive web design, web mockups integration, React/VueJS components' development

PwC 2017 - 2019

ACCOUNTANT

- Accounting production and audit for client portfolio: accounting entries, tax and social returns, full production and audit of tax reports and accounting statements
- Assistance in the production of consolidated

 accounts



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

PANTHEON-SORBONNE UNIVERSITY 2020 - 2021



DESCARTES

ASSOCIATE DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

PARIS-DESCARTES INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY 2019-2020

ADVANCED DIPLOMA IN ACCOUNTING & MANAGEMENT (DSCG)

PARIS-CRÉTEIL-VERSAILLES NATIONAL ACADEMY 2018

MASTER OF FINANCE AND ACCOUNTING

PARIS OUEST NANTERRE LA DÉFENSE
UNIVERSITY
2015-2017

Paris Ouest
Nanterre La Défense